# **Celeste Davis**

Wilmington, DE - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Celeste-Davis/353facb5c6134a5b

To successfully obtain a position within a company that allows me to utilize my current Customer Service, Management and Hospitality skills, while looking forward to a new, challenging and rewarding experience.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Catering Attendant**

Flik Hospitality - Wilmington, NC - February 2016 to Present

Prepare, Deliver and set up all assigned caterings in a timely fashion.

# **Hospitality Specialist**

Eurest Dining Services - Wilmington, NC - November 2010 to January 2016

Hospitality

- \* Worked directly with refreshment vendors. (i.e. Coca Cola, Pepsi, Canteen Refreshments)
- \* Responsible for ordering and managing pantry inventories (including milk, coffee, as well as paper and plastic products).
- \* Assisted local Administrative Assistants with meeting logistics.
- \* Worked directly with the on-site café. Assisted with food displays and managing the cash register on an as needed basis.
- \* Responsible for back-up and alternate relief of receptionist. Directing incoming calls, greeting visitors, and all other related services.

# **Customer Service Specialist**

HSBC Retail Services - October 2005 to April 2010

Provided accurate account information as pertained to each cardholder.

- \* Responded quickly and accurately to customer concerns.
- \* Possess strong problem solving skills, ability to multi-task and proficient with computers.
- \* Tactfully handled confrontational or stressful interactions with the public.

## **EDUCATION**

# Diploma in Buisness

Wilmington High School - Wilmington, NC 1996 to 1999

#### MILITARY SERVICE

Service Country: US

Branch: United States Navy

Rank: E5

August 1999 to August 2005

Operations Specialist worked with Combat Information Center